Christopher Moore collection of Indian Neck Folk Festival and other recordings
American Folklife Center, Library of Congress
Christopher Moore collection of Indian Neck Folk Festival and other recordings 1959-1982 1964-1975
AFC 2016/055
Moore, Christopher
203 items
1 container
.5 linear feet
1 folder (39 sheets)
164 sound tape reels: analog; 7 in.
American Folklife Center, Library of Congress Washington, D.C.
Collection of audio recordings of performances at the Indian Neck Folk Festival from about 1965-1972, as well as at concerts and informal folk music events in Connecticut, in Cambridge, Massachusetts, and the 1968 Old-Time Fiddlers Contest in Craftsbury Common, Vermont. Bulk of the recordings were made from 1964 to 1975, a few in 1982.
Provenance
Christopher Moore; Donation; 2016.
Accruals
No accruals are expected.
Related Material
The following collection is located at the American Folklife Center, Library of Congress:
Indian Neck Folk Festival collection (AFC 2016/002)
Christopher Moore recorded many of the early Indian Neck Folk Festival concerts and events, and also recorded at other venues. He dubbed copies of an unidentified number of the original INFF recordings to cassette, and gave them to the Indian Neck Folk Festival organization. The Indian Neck Folk Festival collection (AFC 2016/002) includes these recordings. The original recordings remain with the current collection.
Access and Restrictions
The collection is open to research. To request materials, please contact the Folklife Reading Room at https://hdl.loc.gov/loc.afc/folklife.contact
Certain restrictions to use or copying of materials may apply.
Administrative History
The Indian Neck Folk Festival was founded by student members of the Yale University Folk Music Club and others and held in 1958, 1960, 1961, 1963, 1965, 1966, and since then usually held annually on a weekend in May. The group raised money for the festival by hosting a series of public folk music concerts in New Haven, Connecticut, and other locations. Around 1970 the non-profit organization cut its ties with Yale. From about 1977 to 1985 the festival administration was based in Harrisburg, Pennsylvania, and hosted a number of concerts there and in other locations, while continuing to hold the Indian Neck Folk Festival, by invitation only, in Falls Village, Connecticut. Audio engineer Christopher Moore recorded some of the earlier festivals and other concerts.
Biographical Note
Christopher Moore (1943-2022) was interested in audio electronics since childhood. While at Yale (Class of 1965), and for a time thereafter, he recorded some of the earliest Indian Neck Folk Festival concerts and events. He used his own money to make the recordings, with the understanding that he provide copies to the Indian Neck Folk Festival organization. These are included in the Indian Neck Folk Festival collection (AFC 2016/002). In addition, he recorded musicians as they worked in the studio, such as Rick and Lorraine Lee, Andy Woolf, and Lou Houck. Outside of his work as an audio engineer, he was a well-known and respected developer of the Space Station SST-282 (for signal delay and reverb) and a consultant to companies interested in audio technology research.
Scope and Content
Collection of audio recordings of performances at the Indian Neck Folk Festival from about 1965-1972, as well as at concerts and informal folk music events in Connecticut, in Cambridge, Massachusetts, and the 1968 Old-Time Fiddlers Contest in Craftsbury Common, Vermont. Bulk of the recordings were made from 1964 to 1975, a few in 1982.
Arrangement
The collection is organized in two series:
Series 1: Manuscripts associated with sound recordings
Series 2: Sound recordings
Selected Search Terms
The following terms have been used to index the description of this collection in the LC Catalog. They are grouped by name of person or organization, by subject or location, and by occupation and listed alphabetically.
People
Abramowitz, Maxine; Apollonio, Nick; Arnoldi, Paul; Badeaux, Ed, 1926-2015; Baez, Joan; Bauhan, Sarah; Berkeley, Roy, 1935-2009; Blaustein, Richard; Block, Allan, 1923-2013; Bok, Gordon; Buchanan, Ian (Musician); Burke, John, 1943-; Cadwell, Paul; Carns, Barbara, 1926-2002; Childs, Peter Olney; Cline, Dallas; Coffey, John, 1940-2016; Corey, Elwin; Davis, Gary, 1896-1972; Dubea, Merle; Elliott, Jack, 1931-; Epstein, Jerry; Fegy, Dick; Feldman, Arnie; Fratar, Gail; Freeman, Ed; Gagne, Joe; Grey, Sara; Guillette, Wilfred; Hamilton, William S.; Haslam, Cliff; Jones, David (Folk singer); Kalb, Danny; Keith, Bill, 1939-2015; Keller, Shirley (Guitarist); Kilberg, Lionel; Kiphuth, Dave; Kosek, Kenny; Lee, Lorraine; Lee, Rick; Loring, Ray; Luce, Harold; Lyman, Mel; MacArthur, Dan; MacArthur, Margaret, 1928-2006; Mallach, Alan; Marash, Dave; Marash, Megan; Martin, Reed (Banjoist); May, Andy; McGrath, Jim (Folk singer); Metz, Don, 1940-; Moore, Christopher H., 1943-2022; Muir, Ann Mayo; Nagler, Eric; Noyes, Geoff; Orzechowski, Jane; Paley, Tom; Parmley, Jack; Paton, Caroline; Peirce, Maggi Kerr, 1931-; Ploof, Ozzie; Rhoads, Mary Faith; Rooney, Jim, 1938-; Rose, Artie; Rosenbaum, Art; Rossi, Neil; Royer, Bill; Rutherford, Betsy; Sainte-Marie, Buffy; Sandberg, Larry; Schotten, Yizhak; Scott, Molly; Scoville, Jon; Siggins, Bob; Silber, Marc; Smith, Ralph Lee, 1927-; Spence, Bill (Musician); Sprung, Roger; Strange, Rusty; Sudhalter, Carol; Traum, Happy; Trickett, Ed; Tuft, Harry M.; Ungar, Jay; Ward, George (Guitarist); Ward, Vaughn; Warner, Jeff (Musician); Washburn, Tony; Watson, Doc; Wernick, Pete, 1946-; West, Harry, 1926-; West, Jeanie, 1933-; Wilcox, Jon; Williams, Big Joe, 1903-1982; Winston, Winnie; Woodbridge, Tim; Woolf, Andy; Wright, Charlie; Young, Wayne (Fiddler)
Organizations
Cappella Cordina; Golden Nectar Goodtime Band; Indian Neck Folk Festival.; Indian Neck Folk Festival.; Mother Bay State Entertainers; New Strangers (Musical group); Pennywhistlers (Musical group); Solomon's Seal (Musical group)
Subjects
Ballads, English.; Bluegrass music.; Blues (Music)--1961-1970.; Fiddle tunes.; Fiddling--Competitions--Vermont.; Folk festivals--Connecticut.; Folk music festivals--Connecticut.; Folk music.; Folk songs, English.; Old-time music.; Popular music--1961-1970.; Popular music--1971-1980.
Places
Cambridge (Mass.); Craftsbury (Vt.); Falls Village (Conn.); New Haven (Conn.)
Form/Genre
Field recordings.
Container List
- Series 1: Manuscript materials associated with sound recordings
  - Subseries 1: Manuscripts from sound recording containers (Box-folder 1/1)
    Each item includes information, in varying degrees of completeness, of song titles, performers, locations, and/or dates. Manuscript materials came from tape containers for SR002, SR082, SR084, SR088-SR091, SR101, SR108-SR109, SR111-SR112, SR116-SR118, SR120-SR123, SR129-SR130, SR135-SR136, SR138, SR144-145, SR147, SR152, and SR163.
  - Subseries 2: Original tape boxes (Box-folders 1/2-3)
    These include the original tape boxes for SR084 and SR085 (the Joan Baez recordings).
- Series 2: Sound recordings
  Performer names are transcribed from tape boxes, corrected if misspelled, and in some cases augmented or completed by information in the Indian Neck Folk Festival collection (AFC 2016/002) and elsewhere. Some names on the tape boxes could not be readily transcribed. The names of some performers are announced on the recordings but not documented on the tape boxes, and sometimes performers listed on the tape box are not found on the recordings.
  - Subseries 1: Indian Neck Folk Festival
    - Indian Neck Folk Festival, #1, May 29, 1964, AFC 2016/055: SR001; RXK 4184; 1 sound tape reel (polyester, 00:33:40): analog, 7 1/2 ips, half track, stereo; 7 in.
      Scope and content: Grey Sky Boys (Don Metz, Roger Last, Gary Audette); Willow Ridge Ramblers.
    - Indian Neck Folk Festival, #2, May 29, 1964, AFC 2016/055: SR002; RXK 4185; 1 sound tape reel (polyester, 00:37:07): analog, 7 1/2 ips, half track, stereo; 7 in.; Numerous audio glitches occur throughout the tape, and are part of the original recording.
    - Indian Neck Folk Festival, #3, May 29, 1964, AFC 2016/055: SR003; RXK 4186; 1 sound tape reel (polyester, 00:14:45): analog, 7 1/2 ips, half track, stereo; 7 in.; Track 5 is a brief snippet of the original content of the tape.
      Scope and content: Grey Sky Boys; Willow Ridge Ramblers. Original ID number: S-28.
    - Indian Neck Folk Festival, A1, May 1, 1965, AFC 2016/055: SR014; RXK 4197; 1 sound tape reel (polyester, 00:30:30): analog, 7 1/2 ips, half track, stereo; 7 in.; Microphone issues occur throughout, causing bad transients in the right channel.; SR014 and SR004 have overlapping content.
      Scope and content: Keith and Rooney [Bill Keith and Jim Rooney]; Karl Eklund; Kirk Smallman Trio with Anne Johnston, David McAllister. Original ID number: S-54.
    - Indian Neck Folk Festival, TB #1, May 1, 1965, AFC 2016/055: SR004; RXK 4187; 1 sound tape reel (polyester, 00:31:00): analog, 7 1/2 ips, half track, stereo; 7 in.; SR014 and SR004 have overlapping content.
      Scope and content: Karl Eklund; Kirk Smallman Trio with Annie Johnston; Dave McAllister; Paul Arnoldi. Original ID number: S-46.
    - Indian Neck Folk Festival, A2, May 1, 1965, AFC 2016/055: SR015; RXK 4198; 1 sound tape reel (polyester, 00:29:25): analog, 7 1/2 ips, half track, stereo; 7 in.; Microphone issues occur throughout, causing bad transients in the right channel.; SR015 and SR005 have overlapping content.
      Scope and content: Paul Arnoldi; Tim Woodbridge, Susie Leicester, Dick Blaustein, Lew Sellinger, and Roy Berkeley (string band); Roy Berkeley. Original ID number: S-55.
    - Indian Neck Folk Festival, TB #2, May 1, 1965, AFC 2016/055: SR005; RXK 4188; 1 sound tape reel (polyester, 00:29:00): analog, 7 1/2 ips, half track, stereo; 7 in.; SR015 and SR005 have overlapping content.
      Scope and content: Paul Arnoldi; Tim Woodbridge, Susie Leicester, Dick Blaustein, Lew Sellinger, and Roy Berkeley (string band); Roy Berkeley. Original ID number: S-47.
    - Indian Neck Folk Festival, TB #3, May 1, 1965, AFC 2016/055: SR006; RXK 4189; 1 sound tape reel (polyester, 00:27:40): analog, 7 1/2 ips, half track, stereo; 7 in.; SR006, SR007, and SR017 have overlapping content.
      Scope and content: Harry and Jeanie West; Jim Field. Original ID number: S-48.
    - Indian Neck Folk Festival, TB #4, May 1, 1965, AFC 2016/055: SR007; RXK 4190; 1 sound tape reel (polyester, 00:31:55): analog, 7 1/2 ips, half track, stereo; 7 in.; The last song is incomplete (the tape ran out during the original recording).; SR006, SR007, and SR017 have overlapping content.
      Scope and content: Jim Field; John Cook, Bob Siggins, Gary Audette; Barry Cogo. Paul Cadwell's name is announced after Jim Field's performance (about 00:07:33) but his name does not appear on the tape box and the performance seems to have been edited out. Original ID number: S-49.
    - Indian Neck Folk Festival, A4, May 1, 1965, AFC 2016/055: SR017; RXK 4200; 1 sound tape reel (polyester, 00:32:25): analog, 7 1/2 ips, half track, stereo; 7 in.; The end of SR006 and the beginning of SR017 overlap. The last track ends mid-song due to the tape running out during the original recording.; SR006, SR007, and SR017 have overlapping content. SR017 and SR018 have approximately the same content. See SR007 for the note about Paul Cadwell's performance.
      Scope and content: Jim Field; John Cook, Bob Siggins, Gary Audette; Barry Cogo. Original ID number: S-57.
    - Indian Neck Folk Festival, A5, May 1, 1965, AFC 2016/055: SR018; RXK 4201; 1 sound tape reel (polyester, 00:31:15): analog, 7 1/2 ips, half track, stereo; 7 in.; SR017 and SR018 have approximately the same content.
      Scope and content: Jim Field; John Cook, Bob Siggins, Gary Audette; Barry Cogo. Paul Cadwell's name is announced after Jim Field's performance (about 00:10:06) but his name does not appear on the tape box and the performance seems to have been edited out. The names of Ed Freeman, Molly Scott, and Gary Audette appear on the tape box but are not on this recording. Note: the reel is labeled S-5. Original ID number: S-58.
    - Indian Neck Folk Festival, TB #5, May 1, 1965, AFC 2016/055: SR008; RXK 4191; 1 sound tape reel (polyester, 00:31:33): analog, 7 1/2 ips, half track, stereo; 7 in.; Gillingham is Molly Scott's husband, and one of the primary founders of the festival. His name is not documented on the tape box, but Scott announces him on the recording.
      Scope and content: Molly Scott with Gary Audette; Peter Gillingham. Original ID number: S-50.
    - Indian Neck Folk Festival, TB #6, May 1, 1965, AFC 2016/055: SR009; RXK 4192; 1 sound tape reel (polyester, 00:29:00): analog, 7 1/2 ips, half track, stereo; 7 in.
      Scope and content: Steve Arkin, Eric Nagler, Artie Rose (guitar), Gary Audette (bass); Happy Traum; Larry Sandburg with Happy Traum. Original ID number: S-51.
    - Indian Neck Folk Festival, TB #7, May 1, 1965, AFC 2016/055: SR010; RXK 4193; 1 sound tape reel (polyester, 00:29:30): analog, 7 1/2 ips, half track, stereo; 7 in.; SR010 and SR020 have the same content.
      Scope and content: Larry Sandburg; Tom Erwin and his Swamp Rats; Jon Scoville; Danny Kalb with Mark Silber (second guitar). Original ID number: S-52.
    - Indian Neck Folk Festival, A7, May 1, 1965, AFC 2016/055: SR020; RXK 4203; 1 sound tape reel (polyester, 00:29:30): analog, 7 1/2 ips, half track, stereo; 7 in.; SR010 and SR020 have the same content.
      Scope and content: Larry Sandburg; Tom Erwin and the Swamp Rats; Jon Scoville; Danny Kalb with Mark Silber (second guitar). Original ID number: S-60.
    - Indian Neck Folk Festival, A8, May 1, 1965, AFC 2016/055: SR021; RXK 4204; 1 sound tape reel (polyester, 00:31:22): analog, 7 1/2 ips, half track, stereo; 7 in.; SR21 and SR011 have approximately the same content, with slightly more content at the beginning and end of SR21 than SR011. See SR022 for the continuation and end of the content on this tape.
      Scope and content: Danny Kalb; Three Billy Goats Gruff Minus One (Harvey Blau and Dave Howard); Jerry Corbett and Mel Lyman; Mel Lyman (harmonica solo). Original ID number: S-61.
    - Indian Neck Folk Festival, TB #8, May 1, 1965, AFC 2016/055: SR011; RXK 4194; 1 sound tape reel (polyester, 00:32:00): analog, 7 1/2 ips, half track, stereo; 7 in.; SR021 and SR011 have approximately the same content, with slightly more content at the beginning and end of SR21 than SR011. See SR022 for the continuation and end of the content on this tape.
      Scope and content: Danny Kalb; Three Billy Goats Gruff Minus One (Harvey Blau and Dave Howard); Jerry Corbett and Mel Lyman; Mel Lyman (harmonica solo). In the last minutes of the recording two dogs can be heard barking. Original ID number: S-53.
    - Indian Neck Folk Festival, A9, May 1, 1965, AFC 2016/055: SR022; RXK 4205; 1 sound tape reel (polyester, 00:05:19): analog, 7 1/2 ips, half track, stereo; 7 in.; This recording has the continuation and end of content heard in the last few minutes of SR021 and SR011.
      Scope and content: Mel Lyman (harmonica solo). Original ID number: S-62.
    - Indian Neck Folk Festival, A3, May 1, 1965, AFC 2016/055: SR016; RXK 4199; 1 sound tape reel (polyester, 00:27:30): analog, 7 1/2 ips, half track, stereo; 7 in.
      Scope and content: Roy Berkeley; Allan Block, Dick Blaustein; Harry and Jeanie West, with Art Rose (dobro). Original ID number: S-56.
    - Indian Neck Folk Festival, A6, May 1, 1965, AFC 2016/055: SR019; RXK 4202; 1 sound tape reel (polyester, 00:27:47): analog, 7 1/2 ips, half track, stereo; 7 in.
      Scope and content: Steve Arkin, Eric Vogler, Art Rose, Gary Audette; Steve Arkin; Happy Traum; Larry Sandburg with Happy Traum. Original ID number: S-59.
    - Indian Neck Folk Festival, #1, May 22, 1965, AFC 2016/055: SR012; RXK 4195; 1 sound tape reel (polyester, 00:42:10): analog, 7 1/2 ips, half track, stereo; 7 in.
      Scope and content: Big Joe Williams. Note: the reel is labeled S-71. Reel 1 from this concert. See SR013 for reel 2. Original ID number: S-64.
    - Indian Neck Folk Festival, #2, May 22, 1965, AFC 2016/055: SR013; RXK 4196; 1 sound tape reel (polyester, 00:46:41): analog, 7 1/2 ips, half track, stereo; 7 in.
      Scope and content: Big Joe Williams. See SR012 for reel 1. Original ID number: S-63.
    - Indian Neck Folk Festival, #0 [sic], April 29, 1966, AFC 2016/055: SR023; RXK 4206; 1 sound tape reel (polyester, Side A: 00:45:00, Side B: 00:31:19): analog, 7 1/2 ips, half track, mono; 7 in.; Side B includes a racist song (track 9; both title and lyrics).
      Scope and content: Lew Sellinger; Dick Blaustein; Tim Woodbridge; Pete Peterson; John MacDonald; John Burke; Bob Bell. The tape box spine is labeled #0 and the tape box back is labeled #1. Original ID number: S-94.
    - Indian Neck Folk Festival, #-1 [sic], April 29, 1966, AFC 2016/055: SR024; RXK 4207; 1 sound tape reel (polyester, Side A: 00:45:50, Side B: 00:45:50): analog, 7 1/2 ips, half track, mono; 7 in.
      Scope and content: Tim Woodbridge; Allan Block; Dave Kiphuth; Dick Blaustein; Pete Peterson; Annie Feldman; John Burke; Roger Sprung; Bob Bell. The box is labeled #2. Original ID number: S-93.
    - Indian Neck Folk Festival, #1, April 30, 1966, AFC 2016/055: SR025; RXK 4208; 1 sound tape reel (polyester, 00:47:15): analog, 7 1/2 ips, half track, stereo; 7 in.
      Scope and content: Dick Blaustein, Tim Woodbridge; Thomas Heimes; The Diminished Seventh; Richard Joffee. Original ID number: S-95.
    - Indian Neck Folk Festival, #2, April 30, 1966, AFC 2016/055: SR026; RXK 4209; 1 sound tape reel (polyester, 00:43:00): analog, 7 1/2 ips, half track, stereo; 7 in.
      Scope and content: Ohio River Boys with Geoff Noyes and Jack Hubert; Dan Isaacson and family; Roy Berkeley; Shirley Keller; Karl Eklund. Original ID number: S-96.
    - Indian Neck Folk Festival, #3, April 30, 1966, AFC 2016/055: SR027; RXK 4210; 1 sound tape reel (polyester, 00:44:00): analog, 7 1/2 ips, half track stereo; 7 in.
      Scope and content: The Pennywhistlers (three of the members), with Art Rose; David and Megan Marash (with Charlie [Charles] Cardini playing harmonica on "Talking to You"); Ed Freeman; The Mother Bay State Entertainers. Paul Cadwell's name appears on the tape box, with the note "no tape." Original ID number: S-97.
    - Indian Neck Folk Festival, #4, April 30, 1966, AFC 2016/055: SR028; RXK 4211; 1 sound tape reel (polyester, 00:46:00): analog, 7 1/2 ips, half track, stereo; 7 in.
      Scope and content: Roger Sprung; Rick and Lorraine Lee; Ed Badeaux; Old Time Duet (Art Rosenbaum and Allan Block); Ana Perez with Charles [Charlie] Cardini and Peter Childs; Peter Childs; Original ID number: S-98.
    - Indian Neck Folk Festival, #5, April 30, 1966, AFC 2016/055: SR029; RXK 4212; 1 sound tape reel (polyester, 00:48:32): analog, 7 1/2 ips, half track, stereo; 7 in.; After 00:40:15, the file consists of audio fragments found after the intended recording ends. The additional audio is of a live Rev. Gary Davis concert, various tones, and a snippet of an aircheck from WDRC-AM-FM radio in 1966.; Either Sherman or Peterson mention a song by Richard and Mimi Farina that Sherman and Peterson proceeded to play. Ironically, the date of the recording is the date on which Richard Farina passed away.
      Scope and content: Pete Childs; Brock Sherman and Pete Peterson; Ray Prinz, Geoff Noyes, Bob Jones, and Jack Hubert; Jim Rooney with Clay Jackson; Arnold Feldman, Dick Blaustein, Billy [last name not documented], and an unidentified musician; Rev. Gary Davis. Original ID number: S-99.
    - Indian Neck Folk Festival, #6, April 30, 1966, AFC 2016/055: SR030; RXK 4213; 1 sound tape reel (polyester, 00:48:47): analog, 7 1/2 ips, half track, stereo; 7 in.
      Scope and content: Jim Scoville; Bob Jones; Jack Parmley and Company (The Bow Street Irregulars); Mel Lyman. Original ID number: S-100.
    - Indian Neck Folk Festival, #7, April 30, 1966, AFC 2016/055: SR031; RXK 4214; 1 sound tape reel (polyester, 00:48:58): analog, 7 1/2 ips, half track, stereo; 7 in.; At 16:59:00 the logged program ends and a fragmented aircheck of Murray The "K" on WOR-FM, NY fills the rest of the tape (and file). The date is unknown but is definitely the week of June 12, 1967, due to comments Murray makes about The Doors appearing at a show with them (WOR) "this past Sunday."
      Scope and content: Mel Lyman. Original ID number: S-101.
    - Indian Neck Folk Festival, #1, May 14, 1967, AFC 2016/055: SR032; RXK 4215; 1 sound tape reel (polyester, 00:36:45): analog, 7 1/2 ips, half track, stereo; 7 in.
      Scope and content: Bill Hamilton and the Ohio River Boys; Lew Sellinger; Bob Merrick. Original ID number: S-103.
    - Indian Neck Folk Festival, #2, May 14, 1967, AFC 2016/055: SR033; RXK 4216; 1 sound tape reel (polyester, 00:42:33): analog, 7 1/2 ips, half track, stereo; 7 in.
      Scope and content: Roy Berkeley; Strict Temperance String Band (Allan Block, Ralph Lee Smith, Andy May, Eric Nagler); Mary Jo Olson. Continued on SR034. Original ID number: S-104.
    - Indian Neck Folk Festival, #3, May 14, 1967, AFC 2016/055: SR034; RXK 4217; 1 sound tape reel (polyester, 00:42:00): analog, 7 1/2 ips, half track, stereo; 7 in.
      Scope and content: Mary Jo Olson; Rick and Lorraine Lee; Ana Perez; John Burke. Continued from SR033. Original ID number: S-105.
    - Indian Neck Folk Festival, #4, May 14, 1967, AFC 2016/055: SR035; RXK 4218; 1 sound tape reel (polyester, 00:29:12): analog, 7 1/2 ips, half track, stereo; 7 in.
      Scope and content: Roger Sprung and his group (Jack Lund, Dave Kiphuth; Arnie Feldman playing on at least one song); Ed Freeman. Continued on SR036. Original ID number: S-106.
    - Indian Neck Folk Festival, #5, May 14, 1967, AFC 2016/055: SR036; RXK 4219; 1 sound tape reel (polyester, 00:41:27): analog, 7 1/2 ips, half track, stereo; 7 in.
      Scope and content: Ed Freeman; High Tension Tim and his Live Wires (Tim Woodbridge, Arnie Feldman, Dick Blaustein, John Burke, Rosemary Blaustein); Jim Bennett. Continued from SR035; continued on SR037. Original ID number: S-107.
    - Indian Neck Folk Festival, #6, May 14, 1967, AFC 2016/055: SR037; RXK 4220; 1 sound tape reel (polyester, 00:44:40): analog, 7 1/2 ips, half track, stereo; 7 in.
      Scope and content: Jim Bennett; Steve Mantoza [or Moitozo]; Pete Peterson. Continued from SR036. Original ID number: S-108.
    - Indian Neck Folk Festival, #7, May 14, 1967, AFC 2016/055: SR038; RXK 4221; 1 sound tape reel (polyester, 00:38:30): analog, 7 1/2 ips, half track, stereo; 7 in.
      Scope and content: Karl Eklund; Shirley Keller; Shire Folk; Ana Perez, Ed Freeman. Original ID number: S-109.
    - Indian Neck Folk Festival: field recordings, May 14, 1967, AFC 2016/055: SR039; RXK 4222; 1 sound tape reel (polyester, Track 1: 00:48:49, Track 2: 00:33:38, Track 3: 00:48:41): analog, 7 1/2 ips, quarter track, mono; 7 in.
      Scope and content: Field recordings (as opposed to formal concerts) from the festival. Track 1: Includes sound checks and snippets of music. Most of the selections are instrumental, and usually feature banjo or fiddle playing. Recorded by Doug Tuchman. Original ID number: S-110.
    - Indian Neck Folk Festival, TBII #1, April 26, 1968, AFC 2016/055: SR047; RXK 4230; 1 sound tape reel (polyester, 00:48:03): analog, 7 1/2 ips, half track, stereo; 7 in.
      Scope and content: Allan Block, Don Howard, Pete Peterson, Jack Lund, John Burke, Sandy Kaplan (banjo), Ralph Lee Smith (harp and dulcimer); John Burke, Dave Howard, Ralph Lee Smith, Art Rosenbaum. Original ID number: S-123.